Let us now learn how to get started using Bootstrap in a web project.
接下来让我们学习如何 在一个万维网项目中应用 Bootstrap
In a exercise that follows this lecture you will get some hands
而在这节课后的练习中 你将会实际体验
on experience of using Bootstrap in a real web project.
在一个真正的 web 项目中 应用 Bootstrap
To get started using Bootstrap we have three possible approaches.
开始使用 Bootstrap 有三种可能的方法
First, you can go to the Bootstrap website and then download the Bootstrap files.
其一 你可以去到 Bootstrap 的网站 并从中下载相应的文件
Second, you can get hold of the Bootstrap sources In either Less or
其二 你可以下载 Bootstrap 的 Less 版本
Sass preprocessor format.
或是 Sass 版本
We will examine these in more detail later on in this course.
我们会在后续课程中详细介绍这种方法
The third alternative for you is to use the precompiled
其三就是使用 Bootstrap CDN
Bootstrap available through Bootstrap CDN.
它含有事先编译好的 Bootstrap
Here, you don't need to download any files, but instead,
这里你无需下载任何文件
simply link to the Bootstrap
取而代之是通过文件分布网络
files that are available through a content distribution network site.
直接链接到 Bootstrap 文件
We will follow the first approach.
我们将会使用第一种方法
In the exercise that follows this lecture.
在接下来的练习中
We will go to the Bootstrap site and then download the Bootstrap files and
我们将会去到 Bootstrap 的网站 并从中下载所需的 Bootstrap 文件
then unzip the downloaded zip file containing the Bootstrap files.
然后我们会解压 我们下载下来的压缩包
When you unzip the zip file, you will find that
解压完之后 你会发现它含有
it creates a folder and subfolders inside the folder.
若干个子文件夹
The structure of the Bootstrap folder is shown on the right side, here.
其总体架构如右图所示
You have subfolders, CSS that contains some Bootstrap CSS files.
其一子文件夹名为 CSS 它含有 Bootstrap 的 CSS 文件
Then you have a subfolder named JS that contains the JavaScript,
其一子文件夹名为 JS
part of the bootstrap sources.
它含有的是 Bootstrap 的 JavaScript 文件
And then you have a subfolder contain, called fonts,
还有一文件夹名为 fonts
which contains fonts that you use in bootstrap.
它含有 Bootstrap 所需的字体
We need to include these files into our Bootstrap project.
我们需要将所有这些文件 引入到我们的项目中
How do we get started using Bootstrap within our project?
那么怎么开始在我们的项目中使用 Bootstrap 呢?
In your HTML5, in the head of your HTML5,
我们需要在 HTML5 代码的 head 标签下面
you are required to include these three lines.
写入这三行代码
Later on, we will examine what these three lines do for your project.
我们会在后面解释这三行代码 具体是干啥的
Then, you need to input the bootstrap CSS files into your web page.
然后 你需要在你的网页中引入 Bootstrap 的 CSS
To do that, we will include these two lines into the head of an HTML page.
我们需要在 head 标签下面引入下面两条代码
Now, we are importing the Bootstrap file itself and then, the Bootstrap theme
现在我们通过如下两行代码来引入Bootstrap
CSS file into our project using these two lines.
和 Bootstrap 主题的 CSS 文件
You notice that I have specified the files as bootstrap.min.css and
你大概注意到我用的文件是bootstrap.min.css 和
bootstrap-theme.min.css.
bootstrap-theme.min.css
The minfied format is what we use when we design our project.
我们的项目设计将用这种减缩版本
Now if you are editing a Bootstrap or a CSS file,
一般而言我们在编辑一个Bootstrap 或 CSS 代码时
you will write the CSS file in normal format.
使用的是正常的格式
Then you can strip off all the unnecessary blank spaces and
然后减缩是指 将所有不必要的 空格 空行以及所有注释
the comments from your CSS file and then create a minified file.
从而能有效地压缩文件的大小
So, the verified file is much smaller in size and so
压缩文件大小是为了 让用户能够更轻易地将其下载下来
easier for people to download when they view your web page.
从而能有效地提升网页的加载速度
In addition, Bootstrap also uses Javascript.
Bootstrap 还应用了 JavaScript
Bootstrap makes use of the jQuery Javascript library for
事实上它大部分都在利用 JavaScript 中的
providing much of its Javascript functionality.
jQuery 库
So Bootstrap has JavaScript plugins
所以 Bootstrap 是有 JavaScript 插件的
designed using the jQuery library as the basis.
这些插件正是用 jQuery 设计出来的
So that is the reason you need to include the jQuery library.
这就是为什么你还需要引入 jQuery 的库
In addition, you will include Bootstraps own JavaScript classes,
当然了 我们也要引入 Bootstrap 自身的 JavaScript 文件
this has to be done just before the end of the body of your web page.
注意 引入这些文件的位置 是在 body 标签的底部之前
The primary reason why we include the JavaScript files towards
之所以要在靠近底部才引用
the end of the body of your web page, is so that when you view the web page,
是因为当你浏览网页时
the web page can be rendered even before the JavaScript is actually processed.
即使 JavaScript 还没有处理完毕 网页就已经能呈现了
So, when your web page is being rendered by your browser, it'll first display all
所以如果你在底部才引用的话 浏览器就会先呈现你的网页
the content and then use JavaScript to then restyle the content.
然后再用 JavaScript 来调整内容的格调
Now, this makes the web page loading a lot more faster.
可以想象 这可以让你 网页的加载速度大大提升
As I mentioned earlier,
我之前说过
you can also include Bootstrap directly from its Bootstrap CDN.
你可以通过使用 Bootstrap CDN 来引用 Bootstrap
This is the set of lines that you will include within your HTML
如果你确实想这么做
page in order to use Bootstrap directly from the content distribution network.
你就可以引用这些代码
So the first two lines you will include in the head to import the CSS files.
所以在网页 head 部分的前两行是 引入 Bootstrap 的 CSS 文件
The last two lines will be included at the bottom of the body of your HTML
而在HTML页面body部分的后面则用于引入
page to import the JavaScript libraries.
两行JavaScript 代码库
Now, when you design a web page, we will often use a class called as a container
在设计网页时通常会用到一个class属性 取值为container
to hold all the contents of our web page.
其将包含网页的整个内容
The container defines the fixed width region within your web page.
这个 container 属性定义网页中一个固定的宽度区域
Inside which the contents will be displayed for your web page.
内容呈现在该区域里面
So this is one way of restricting your contents to display in certain
这是一种方法将网页的内容限制在
part of the web page.
网页的一个特定区域中
The container size will vary depending upon
而至于这个 container 的具体宽度
the size of the screen from which you are viewing your website.
则基本取决于你浏览网页时 所用的显示窗口的大小
We will deal with the container more in the next set of lessons.
我们将会在后续几节课中 学习更多有关 container 的知识
Normally, we would use the container as the outermost
通常 container 一般用于最外层的 div 区段内
div element to wrap the contents of our website.
来封装网页的整体内容
This is required in order to make the Bootstrap grid work correctly.
事实上 为使 Bootstrap 的网格系统正常运作 container 是必需的
What exactly is the Bootstrap grid?
那么什么是 Bootstrap 网格系统呢
That we will deal with in the next
我们将会在
set of lessons where we will deal with responsive web design.
后续的几节有关 响应式网页设计的课中讨论到它
You can also use another class card as container fluid to
你可以用另一称为 container-fluid 的类
use a full width container.
若需要一全屏宽的 container
The container fluid class enables a full width container window,
container-fluid 类允许占满窗口的全部
which spans the entire size of your screen.
而窗口也可占据整个屏幕
To understand the container class better, let me show you a web page.
为使你更好地理解 container 是干嘛的 我将给你看一个网页
You're going to see this web page as part of your exercises later.
该网页在后续练习中你也会接触到
Now, within this web page,
那么在这个网页中
all the contents in here are enclosed inside a container so
所有的这些内容都是 封装在一 container 之内
that they will be displayed inside a fixed region of your screen.
这样显示时 它们被限制在了 网页的某个特定区域中
Bootstrap also provides another class called the row.
Bootstrap 还提供了一个叫 row 的类
We use the row class to divide the page contents into multiple rows.
我们用 row 类来将页的内容分成多行
Each row acts as a horizontal grouping for
每一行都是横向组合一系列
information that has to be displayed in a single group.
需同时显示的信息
A row may contain multiple columns.
每一行会有若干列
We will deal with that in the next lesson.
我们会在后面的课中 学习到相应内容
In Bootstrap, the rows must always be contained inside containers for
在 Bootstrap 中 row 是必须放在 container 里面的
the Bootstrap grid to work correctly.
这样Bootstrap 网格系统才会正常
Another element that we're going to examine in the exercise is a Jumbotron.
我们在练习中还会学习到一个叫 "超大屏幕" 的元素
A Jumbotron is a lightweight
超大屏幕是一个 轻量级的 Bootstrap 组件
Bootstrap component that is used to showcase key content on your web page.
用于展示网页中关键性的内容
So for example, this can be used to show the name of your company,
比如说 你可以用它展示 你公司的名字
some brief description about your company, and typically at the top of your page.
或是你公司的一些简介 通常也是在页面的顶部
When you use a Jumbotron within your web page, you can use the Jumbotron
使用Jumbotron时 可以将其置于一 container 的外面
outside a container and then include a container inside a Jumbotron.
然后在超大屏幕内部 再包含另一个 container
So that the contents of the Jumbotron can be within a fixed region
从而超大屏幕中的内容也能被限制在 超大屏幕的某一特定区域中
of the Jumbotron but this enables your Jumbotron to span the entire screen width.
这样 你的超大屏幕也能 占据整个屏幕的宽度
Returning to our web page example,
回到我们的网页样例
the top blue region is using a Jumbotron and
页面顶部这一大块浅靛蓝色的东西 就是超大屏幕了
inside that we are displaying the contents of our website.
在其中将显示我们网页的 概括性的信息
The name and some brief description of the website.
比如我们网页的名字 以及网页的一些简要介绍
Now, we will move on to our first hands on exercise
那么接下来 我们就要进行 我们的第一次练习了
where you will use the classes the you just encountered.
你将会应用到你刚刚看到的这些类
You will start by including Boostrap into your HTML page and
你会先需要在你的 HTML 中 引入 Bootstrap 框架
then we will use the container and
然后你需要在你的项目中 应用 container 和 row
the rule classes to structure our web page and
来组织网页的结构 你同时还会学习如何
we also see the use of Jumbotron within our web page.
在网页中应用超大屏幕 翻译: Carefree0910 | 审阅: Saul Qunming Yuan Coursera Global Translator Community